export const questions = [
  {
    question_id: 1,
    main_question_stem:
      "In a locality, there are thrice as many buses as cabs. 10% of the buses are air-conditioned while 60% of the cabs are air-conditioned. If there are only these 2 types of vehicles, what percentage of the vehicles are air-conditioned?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: 0.225,
    answer_2: 0.25,
    answer_3: 0.3,
    answer_4: 0.333,
    answer_5: 0.36,
    correct_answer: "A",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Percentage",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 2,
    main_question_stem:
      "In a school, 20% of the boys learn French while 60% of the students who learn French are girls. If there are 100 boys, how many girls learn French?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: 20,
    answer_2: 24,
    answer_3: 30,
    answer_4: 36,
    answer_5: 45,
    correct_answer: "C",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Percentage",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 3,
    main_question_stem:
      "A and B need to do the laundry since their washing machine broke down. A can wash 1/3rd of the clothes in 30 minutes. Both A and B can wash all the clothes in 1 hour. What fraction of the clothes can B wash in 20 minutes?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "1/12",
    answer_2: "1/9",
    answer_3: "1/8",
    answer_4: "1/6",
    answer_5: "1/3",
    correct_answer: "B",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 4,
    main_question_stem:
      "A can write 10 programming codes in 15 hours, and B can write the same codes in 12 hours. If A and B work together on the codes, what fraction of the total work would B have done more than A after 3 hours?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "1/5",
    answer_2: "3/10",
    answer_3: "1/3",
    answer_4: "9/20",
    answer_5: "1/2",
    correct_answer: "D",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 5,
    main_question_stem:
      "A and B can paint 3 walls in 2 hours. Along with C, they can paint 5 walls in 3 hours. If A and C work at the same rate, how long would B take to paint 2 walls?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "1.5 hours",
    answer_2: "1.8 hours",
    answer_3: "2 hours",
    answer_4: "2.5 hours",
    answer_5: "3 hours",
    correct_answer: "A",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 6,
    main_question_stem:
      "Machines A and B can polish 3 articles in 2 hours and 5 articles every 4 hours. If the efficiency of A were tripled and that of B doubled, how long would the 2 machines together take to polish 70 articles?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "10 hours",
    answer_2: "12 hours",
    answer_3: "15 hours",
    answer_4: "16 hours",
    answer_5: "20 hours",
    correct_answer: "A",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 7,
    main_question_stem:
      "A and B can complete a work in 15 days. The same work can be completed by A and C in 20 days. If B is twice as efficient as C, in how many days can A complete the work alone?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "20 days",
    answer_2: "24 days",
    answer_3: "22.5 days",
    answer_4: "27.5 days",
    answer_5: "30 days",
    correct_answer: "E",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 8,
    main_question_stem:
      "A water pipe fills a tank at the rate of 20 litres in every 8 minutes. A second water pipe fills the tank at 20 litres in half the time of the above pipe. The tank capacity is 720 litres and a 3rd pipe along with the above 2 pipes together fill the tank in 80 minutes. At what rate per minute does the 3rd pipe fill?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "1 litre/min",
    answer_2: "1.2 litre/min",
    answer_3: "1.5 litre/min",
    answer_4: "1.6 litre/min",
    answer_5: "1.8 litre/min",
    correct_answer: "C",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 9,
    main_question_stem:
      "A water pipe fills a tank at the rate of 5 litres in every minute. Along with another water pipe, it fills the tank in 30 minutes. If the efficiency of the 2nd pipe were doubled, the time taken to fill the tank along with the 1st pipe would have been 18 minutes. What is the capacity of the tank?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "90 litres",
    answer_2: "105 litres",
    answer_3: "120 litres",
    answer_4: "135 litres",
    answer_5: "150 litres",
    correct_answer: "C",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 10,
    main_question_stem:
      "20 men can do a work in 12 days and 30 women can do double the same work in 36 days. How many days would 8 men and 12 women together take to complete the work?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "6 days",
    answer_2: "8 days",
    answer_3: "12 days",
    answer_4: "16 days",
    answer_5: "18 days",
    correct_answer: "E",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 11,
    main_question_stem:
      "4 people can paint 8 walls in 6 days. The 4 people worked on painting the 8 walls for 2 days. Thereafter, another 2 people joined them. In how many days would the 6 people paint the remaining of the 8 walls?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "4/3 days",
    answer_2: "2 days",
    answer_3: "8/3 days",
    answer_4: "3 days",
    answer_5: "9/2 days",
    correct_answer: "C",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question_id: 12,
    main_question_stem:
      "In a college, 3 automated exam-paper grading machines working at a constant rate, can grade 36 answer sheets per hour. The college installs 1 more automated exam-paper grading machine that is twice as efficient as the ones above. In how many hours can these machines grade 240 answer sheets?",
    subquestion1: "",
    subquestion2: "",
    subquestion3: "",
    answer_1: "2.7 hours",
    answer_2: "3 hours",
    answer_3: "3.6 hours",
    answer_4: "4 hours",
    answer_5: "6 hours",
    correct_answer: "D",
    Category: "Quant",
    "Sub-category": "Rate and Work",
    "Quant_category 1": "Word problems",
    "Quant_category 2": "Arithmetic",
    level: 1,
  },
];
